globalshareware.com 2017-06-27

# GlobalShareWare.com - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to the site [www.globalshareware.com](http://www.globalshareware.com/). All products and services on this site were offered by SOFTISLAND Inc. SOFTISLAND Inc. respect your privacy choices. We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. What is personal information? Generally, this may include your first and last name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number. If you make a purchase from our site, we will need to collect some information to be used only for the purpose of completing your purchase transaction.

**About Personal Identification Information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**About Non-Personal Identification Information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site such as the operating system and the Internet service providers' utilized and other similar information. Web Browser Cookies

[www.globalshareware.com](http://www.globalshareware.com/) may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How We Collect the information**

SOFTISLAND Inc.. May collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  
•To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
•To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
•To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
•To process payments  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.  
•To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.  
•To send periodic emails  
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

**How We Protect Your Information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, user name, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

**Sharing Your Personal Information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes.

**Third Party Websites**

Users may find content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

SOFTISLAND Inc. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Safe Harbor Compliance**

SOFTISLAND Inc.. complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. SOFTISLAND Inc.. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.

**Dispute Resolution**

Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of personal information should be directed to SOFTISLAND Inc. Inc. at the address given above. SOFTISLAND Inc. Inc. will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this Policy. For complaints that cannot be resolved between SOFTISLAND Inc. Inc. and the complainant, SOFTISLAND Inc.. has agreed to participate in the dispute resolution procedures of the panel established by the European data protection authorities to resolve disputes pursuant to the Safe Harbor Principles.

**Security**

When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site, We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. SOFTISLAND Inc. is audited annually and meets SOC2 Type II and HIPAA compliance.

**Contact Us**

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy or if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email [support@globalshareware.com](mailto:support@globalshareware.com)
